<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Aches!</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="forgot_password"><u><i>Forgotten password?</i></u></string>
    <string name="sign_up"><u><i> SIGN UP</i></u></string>
    <string name="sign_in"><u><i> SIGN IN</i></u></string>
    <string name="already">Already a member?</string>
    <string name="not_member">Not a member?</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="sign_up_heading">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="log_in_heading">LOG IN</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="password_help">Find Your Account?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        Let’s Be honest Over here, It’s great phone with top notch camera, Great Software experience and great build quality.

Design is not as good as Samsung Galaxy S8 or note series, Pixel has significant amount of bezels, but Pixel XL is quite good, they have front facing stereo speakers on front so there is bezels on top as well as bottom, They tries something different with active sense technology so you can squeeze your phone and invoke some actions(Like HTC U11), because of those sensors I think side bezels are little bit more compare to other phone, but overall Design is kinda good.

Camera, According to DXoMark , Pixel got 98, highest ever any phone got, its just number but as we all know last year’s pixel was one of the best camera and I think this year also they are not going to disappoint.

Performance is going to be top-notch, direct software updates from google, Stock android, last year’s pixel was one of the fastest phone I have ever used.

Google Perks, unlimited cloud storage, Google Lens, Fast software updates, Google Support etc.

All those reasons make Google Pixel XL a worthy contender of best Phone of the Year.
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
